Wrecking Ball
毁灭球
压制:随Feng
歌手：Miley Cyrus
We clawed, we chained our hearts in vain
我们争执过 我们亲密过 我们已经心力交瘁
We jumped, never asking why
我们的感情进行的太快 却从来没有问过对方为什么
We kissed, I fell under your spell
我们拥吻过 我陷入你的蜜咒里
A love no one could deny
没有人可以否认我的爱
Don't you ever say I just walked away
难道你不曾了解 我虽然离开
I will always want you
可是我依然想跟你在一起
I can't live a lie, running for my life
我不能活在一个左右着我生活的谎言中
I will always want you
我依旧还是想跟你在一起
I came in like a wrecking ball
我像毁灭球一样的闯入
I never hit so hard in love
在任何一段感情 我从没有闯入的如此艰难
All I wanted was to break your walls
我只是想要闯入你的内心
All you ever did was wreck me
你做过的一切已经毁灭了我
Yeah, you wreck me
没错 你毁了我
I put you high up in the sky
我把你放上了天空
And now, you're not coming down
然而现在 你不想落下
It slowly turned, you let me burn
感情慢慢变质 你燃烧了我
And now, we're ashes on the ground
所以现在 我们烧成落在地上的灰
Don't you ever say I just walked away
难道你不曾了解 我虽然离开
I will always want you
我依旧还是想跟你在一起
I can't live a lie, running for my life
我不能活在一个左右着我生活的谎言中
I will always want you
我依旧还是想跟你在一起
I came in like a wrecking ball
我像毁灭球一样的闯入
I never hit so hard in love
在任何一段感情 我从没有闯入的如此艰难
All I wanted was to break your walls
我只是想要闯入你的内心
All you ever did was wreck me
你做过的一切已经毁灭了我
I came in like a wrecking ball
我像毁灭球一样的闯入
Yeah, I just closed my eyes and swung
我紧闭我的双眼 不停摇摆
Left me crouching in a blaze and fall
剩我一个人蜷缩在煎熬和迷失中
All you ever did was wreck me
你做过的一切毁灭了我
Yeah, you wreck me
没错 你毁了我
I never meant to start a war
我从没想过跟你争执
I just wanted you to let me in
我只是想你接受我
And instead of using force
用非暴力的方式
I guess I should've let you in
我想我早该让你赢
I never meant to start a war
我从没想过跟你争执
I just wanted you to let me in
我只是想你接受我
I guess I should've let you in
我想我早该让你赢
Don't you ever say I just walked away
难道你不曾了解 我虽然离开
I will always want you
我依旧还是想跟你在一起
I came in like a wrecking ball
我像毁灭球一样的闯入
I never hit so hard in love
在任何一段感情 我从没有闯入的如此艰难
All I wanted was to break your walls
我只是想要闯入你的内心
All you ever did was wreck me
你做过的一切已经毁灭了我
I came in like a wrecking ball
我像毁灭球一样的闯入
Yeah, I just closed my eyes and swung
我紧闭我的双眼 不停摇摆
Left me crouching in a blaze and fall
你做过的一切已经毁灭了我
All you ever did was wreck me
你做过的一切毁灭了我
Yeah, you wreck me
没错 你毁了我
是的 你毁了我
压制:随Feng